and we will begin
reading from verse
one when you're there please say
amen and the Bible says and the Lord
spake unto Moses saying send thou men
that they may search the land of Canaan
which I give unto the children of Israel
of every tribe of their fathers you
shall send a man everyone a ruler among
them I was
um
really happy up
here uh when I heard the children's
story talking about
spies and I thought to myself that's
exactly what I'm talking about
today
confirmation God told the children of
Israel I need you I want you to send out
12 men
and these men were to spy out the land
of
Canaan when you think of spying out what
comes to
mind what does that mean to spy
out all right to
gather information to
intensely
observe these men were sent to spy out
to to seek out this land of King
Canan and and and and so God says I want
you to choose 12 men now let me ask you
a
question every tribe was to have a
representative now if God were speaking
to us and and they and God said to us
okay Campbell I need you to choose out
men now don't give me
names I'm just asking what would you go
for who would you go for don't no names
but but would you go for men that you
had confidence in yes leadership that
you were like yes this if anyone can do
it this person
can so I want you to imagine how these
the these uh uh the Israelites are
choosing out men but they're not just
choosing any old person they're choosing
like the cream
of the
crow in fact check this out notice with
me verse verse four the Bible says and
these were their names of the tribe of
Reuben Shamu the son of Zach pause for a
second
Shamu you know what that name
means it means
Renown I mean just think about that for
a moment okay renown
that sound like a man of
influence we're going to choose out
Renown because we trust that if if God's
going to use anyone he will use
Renown let me give you the other names
we won't read through all of them but
from Verses 4 all the way down to verse
uh 13 are the names these are the names
shapat it means judge agal it means
Avenger paly it means delivered gel it
means Fortune of God Gotti it means my
fortune Amel it means people of God Seth
means hidden Nai hidden um gel means
Majesty of God Joshua means deliverer
and Caleb means
attack check out those names guys
renowned judge Avenger delivered Fortune
of God my fortune people of God hidden
Majesty of God deliverer attack it was
as if these names represented the very
Promises of
God the promises of God are going before
you to spy out the
land who would not be
confident
knowing that you are
Standing
on the Promises
verse
17 and Moses sent them to spy out of the
land of
Canaan and said unto them get you up
this way Southward and go into the
mountain and see the land what it is and
the people that dwell there wherein they
whether they be strong or weak few or
many and what the land is what they DW
they dwell in whether it be good or bad
and what cities they be that they dwell
in whether in tents or in strongholds
and what the land is whether it be fat
or lean whether there be wood therein or
not and be ye of
what
why why should you be of good
courage because God is with you you are
standing on the the promises of God God
are going before
you so be of good courage and bring of
the fruit of the land now the time was
the time of the first ripe
grapes now that's
significant because if the time is the
time of the first right R right grapes
it means that the vineyard keepers are
out in
mass and so it's going to be even more
of a challenge to actually get into this
land and spy it out because it was a
time where where where where people were
out in Mass where where they might most
likely get
caught but they were told be of good
courage now we're going to do we're
going to do something here that's going
to be a little bit different because I'm
going to need you to imagine that these
12 Spies
have cell
phones walkie talkies if you want to be
military okay so so while they are out
spying we can actually hear what's going
on they are radioing back to
us a and so you know our first thing is
are they even going to get into the land
of
Canaan a a and when we discover that
they are in the land of Canaan we hear
something like we're in and we're in the
camp like what they're in they're
in you don't look
excited they're in yes they got in that
how God is with
us they have gotten into the land and
and now they begin to explore and they
begin to tell us fruit looks
good
but land looks good
and they're going through telling us
everything that's going on while we're
listening we we're listening and we're
hearing them report back to us and we're
just like whoa whoa this is amazing
remember how God led us in the past and
look at what's going on like this is
good stuff and so and so now they they
we lose contact with them for a while
and now they they come back and I want
you to check out verse verse 25 so verse
25 says this they went and came to Moses
and to Aaron and to all the congregation
of the children of Israel unto the
Wilderness of pan to cadesh and brought
back word unto them unto all the
congregation and showed them the fruit
of the land look at this guys you
remember right they brought back those
big gra look at what we brought back let
me ask you what are you feeling right
now come on guys what are you feeling
right
now you got into the land first of all
you got into the land and that was great
but you actually got
out like God was with you the EV the
fact that they came back was that
evidence that God was with
them God had hidden them in enemy
territory
wow the children of Israel were excited
as they hear this news keep reading
verse verse uh uh 2
3 they uh I'm sorry not verse 23 we're
going to go to verse
26 uh and they went and came to Moses uh
to Aaron to all the congregation of the
children of Israel unto the Wilderness
of pan to cadesh and brought back word
unto them and to all the congregation
and showed them the fruit of fruit of
the land and they told him and said we
came unto the land whether thou sentest
us and surely it floweth with milk and
honey and this is the fruit of it amen
just as God had promised remember God
had told them this is a land flowing
with milk and honey and they come back
and they said yes all that God said is
true how do you feel right now you are
excited it's like yes congregation it is
time to
go
amen let's do
this until
we get to verse
28 and in verse
28 we find this
word
nevertheless you know what nevertheless
means it means okay forget about
everything I just
said forget about all that hey look
God's word is true we came in we we we
went in unspotted unspotted we came out
unspotted we are here as evidence that
God is with us and then they turn around
and say
nevertheless the
people be strong that dwell in the land
and the cities are
what walled and very great and moreover
we saw the children children of anad
there and those were
giants the amalekites dwell in the land
of the
South and the Hittites and the jebusites
and the amorites dwell in the
mountains and the Canaanites dwell by
the Sea and by the coast of
Jordan do you see what they've just
done while things may may may may look
good while it may look like God is with
us and I uality what lays ahead of us is
dangerous
territory we can't do
this listen listen I I I we wanted to
report to you the good and we've got
that out the way but now we need to let
you know why we cannot move
forward why we cannot
Advance because there are giants in the
land and by the way if we go in the land
land I want you to know that we will be
surrounded between the mountains and the
coast and the South we will be
surrounded and if an attack happens
there will be no way for us to
escape what ends up happening beloved is
that these spies end up fearing man more
than they fear
God you see the message they should have
come back with was in their very
names they should have come back with
this God is renowned he is our judge he
is our Avenger our deliverer who has
delivered us the fortune of God is my
fortune we are his people he hid us the
Majesty is of God is with us let us
attack
was the message that went in and that
should have been the message that came
out the problem is 10 parts of the 12
messages did
not 10 of those spies did not come back
with the message that they were sent to
deliver instead it was just two who were
the
two Joshua and Caleb Joshua means
deliverer Caleb means
attack the only message of of no guys
wait hold on because you'll read that in
a moment the only two were this the
deliverer
attack everyone else came back no we
can't no we can't we can't go forward we
can't Advance no we
cannot verse 30 and Caleb steal the
people before Moses and said let us do
what let us go up at
once listen to me
Guys these 10 spies returned and said
look the people are stronger than us
they are bigger than us and there are
walls even even before we Face them
there are walls to that City that are so
high that we can't cannot break them
down these are all the reasons why thank
you thank you
cousin these are all the reasons
why we cannot move
forward and Caleb steals the people and
he says no no no hold
on I'm not going to deny that what they
have said is true he didn't say they
were lying
he didn't say there are no walls he
didn't say there are no Giants he didn't
say the Canaanites and and the
amalekites and all these people were in
the land he didn't say any of that he
just said yes I get that yes it's going
to be hard but guess what the deliverer
is with us let us attack
Amen Let us move forward we can and we
will let us go up and possess the land
so look
guys I
know going back to school now there too
many Giants you got to
face making that change now at the job
it's no no no it's too
hard continuing in that marriage that
seems like it's about on the brink of
failure it it's too hard to even think
should I continue
on that career
change that difficulty God telling you
launch out and go for it I know it seems
too difficult but God
says go
up because that's the devil's job the
devil's job is to try to stop you from
moving with
God the devil's job is to try to tell
you all the reasons why you can't and
and God says yes you
can God says yes we can all right don't
think politics with M okay
just we're talking about God God says
yes we can and the devil says no no no
no no no no no no no no no no it's too
difficult you face too many obstacles
you see the reason why Caleb didn't care
was because Caleb's name means
attack y'all not catching this
attack it doesn't matter what the enemy
says attack because Caleb knew who was
on his side yes and beloved listen to me
if God is on your side then who can be
against
you see beloved what what we need to
understand is that is that the only side
to be on is God's side so Satan wants to
make it so that oh it's your side versus
this side beloved listen we need to be
on one side and one side only and that
is God's side because when we're on
God's side guess what we can move
forward we can advance so Caleb was a
fighter he had a fighting Spirit the
other 10 lost their fighting
Spirit Joshua Caleb said we can do this
we can go up and the problem is for many
of us within us we have these 12
Spies and so often the voice of the 10
overpower the voice of the
two no man you can't do that you're
going to
fail you're not good enough you're not
strong enough you're not smart enough
you're not whatever it is you fill in
the blank the voice of the 10 have a
habit of speaking negativity to you to
make you think you
can't let the voice of the
two begin to overpower the voice of the
because all you need to know is that the
deliverer is with you now
attack attack that class that you're
like I'm failing this and I don't know
attack the class because if God is with
you who can be against you beloved we
have to understand that God wants us to
advance to go
forward and often there is this this
thought in our mind that brings us into
captivity When God says no no no no no
you should bring every thought into
captivity to
me and that's what we're trying to do we
wrestle not against flesh and blood our
Warfare is not against flesh and blood
we are to our our uh we are to cast down
imagination bringing every thought into
captivity so don't let yourself tell you
that you
can't don't let yourself tell you that
it's too difficult hear the voice of God
over the voice of
self so what happens there's division in
the
camp you see because 10 are giving one
message and two are giving another 10
are saying do not advance two are saying
advance and the devil knows that when he
can bring division in the camp it stops
the mission of God
so all he needs is that division all he
needs is and check out how this division
happens check out with me verse 31
chapter 13:31 the Bible says but the men
let me read again verse 30 and Caleb
Still the people before Moses and said
let us go up at once and possess it for
we are what able to do what overcome it
we are what everyone we are what
everyone we are able not just able but
to do what to overcome it what a message
coming from Caleb and then check this
out verse
31 but the men that went up with him
said we be not able to go up against the
people for they are stronger than
we and they brought up an evil report of
the land which they had searched unto
the children of Israel saying the land
through which we have gone to search it
it is a land that eateth up the
inhabitants thereof and all the people
that that we saw in it are men of Giant
stature and there we saw the Giants the
sons of anak which come of the Giants
and we were in our own sight as
grasshoppers so we were in their
sight evil has a way of
exaggerating at first was hey the land
is good it's a fruitful land flowing
with milk and
honey oh yeah but you know what there's
some issues there and the issues should
be enough to discourage us to not go up
but when the voice of Caleb came and
said no no no no no we can then they had
to
amplify the
problems listen we were trying to be a
little gentle but let us speak to you
plainly the land eats people up
wow what kind of land must that be that
it actually devours
people remember they had just said the
land is FL with milk and honey now
they're like no the land eats people up
and not only that but we were
grasshoppers in our own sight now let me
ask you a
question if a man by the name of
renowned and Fortune of
God and judge and Avenger begin to tell
you guys we have reason to be afraid
what do you think that
does to the
congregation what what is a congregation
now
thinking hey these are men that we
trust are you with me we would not have
sent them if we did not trust them but
these men lost their faith with God and
now they're coming back and they're
saying no way too impossible and now
you're going to read that the people
were like oh wow God brought us out here
to kill
us you see beloved
listen Satan
knows Satan
knows that if he can bring
division in the
camp then we begin to lose
sight of the very Miss and purpose of
God because you see come with me look at
numbers 14 numbers 14 numbers 14:1 and
all the congregation lifted up their
voice and cried and the people wept that
night pause for a
second who just LED them out of
Egypt God who who open the Red
Sea who reain bread down from heaven for
them
and now the people in the facei of God
are
Weeping
terrified
fear because of the Giants in front of
them the people had lost faith in God
and put their fear in in
man notice with me verse two and all the
children of Israel murmured against
Moses and against Aaron and the whole
congregation said unto them would God
that we had died in the land of Egypt or
would God we had died in this
Wilderness pause for a second
guys there are two destinations there
are two locations in this story where
are
they where are the children of Israel
right now in the wilderness where are
they trying to go
to they they're trying to go to the
promised land
so so there's this
tension there's this decision to be
made do we go
forward or do we stay in the
wilderness or do we
go watch
this verse four and they said one to
another verse three wherefore has the
Lord brought us unto this land to Fall
by The Sword and that our wise not
children should be prayed were it not
better for us to what return into
Egypt and they said one to another let
us uh let us make a captain and let us
return into
Egypt let's go
backward let's go
back because what lays ahead of us is
too
challenging it's too much of a trial
it's too scary it is a huge unknown how
many of you like
unknowns nobody likes
unknowns the reason is because we don't
know how the unknown turns
out so it's easy for us to project our
fears it's even easy for us to project
our successes ah it's going to work no
it's not going to work but the truth is
nobody
knows and that's why we ultimately have
to say God
please deliver us but check this out
guys God cannot deliver us if we're not
all on the same
page see the question might not even be
do we stay here for the moment or do we
Retreat or do we advance the real
question is are we
one because when we're one under God
then God will tell us stay hold on wait
on the the Lord or he might say go up
and possess the
land but if we're not one you understand
what I'm saying then no matter no matter
what decision that we
make there's going to be trouble you'll
see that in the story come come back
with me so so so check this out
guys the question is let me rephrase
it do you know why you're
here do you guys know why you're
here do you know why you are here in
Campbell why you are
here has brought you
here to spy out the
[Laughter]
land God brought you here to spy out the
city he says okay guys I have a mission
for you your mission is to take the
city that's why I've called you here
that's why I moved you here from you
know where you were over in some other
city or some other state or maybe even
some other country you are here right
now because I'm entrusting you with a
mission I need you to spy out the land
so I need you to tell me about I need
you to spy out the city and and the
layout and and what it looks like and
and are there great walls or are there
small walls are there tents is is is the
city penetrable I I need you to check
all of this out why why is God calling
us to spy out this
city because it's
ours it's
hours so he says go and he sends out
spies he says listen I want you to bring
some fruit
back just as
evidence that the city is right for the
taking I want you to bring some
fruit and beloved over the last few
years we have brought fruit back showing
that yes God is getting ready to do
something in this
city yeah hasn't been a raining down of
fruit but look we have evidence that
there are people out there who are
hungering and thirsting after
righteousness we have people out there
who are wanting to know the truth who
are wanting to understand righteousness
and we're seeing the evidence so God
says okay now that you see this evidence
what's what what is the report we're
going to
bring hey guys guess
what God has a mission for us here
Revelation 146 and 7even I saw another
Angel flying in the midst of Heaven
having the Everlasting gospel to preach
unto Every Nation Kindred tongue and
people saying with a loud voice fear God
and give glory to him for the hour of
his judgment is come I have a mission
for you here and that mission is to
bring forth fruit that mission is to
take the city that
Mission San Jose is not like other
places
the walls here
are seemingly
impenetrable people here don't care
about God they don't want to hear about
God people here are rich and incre with
increase with goods and and Pastor or or
church you don't get it we you know we
we just need to be here and maintain and
kind of take care of ourselves you know
just
maintain so so let's just let's just do
that
thing beloved listen to me God wants us
to work and he wants us to work wisely
like don't get me wrong because because
I know that that the heart of Campbell I
believe that the heart of Campbell is
about winning
Souls I believe
that just like I believe these 10 spies
wanted the best for
Israel but they thought maybe this is
not
the way to do
it and beloved what I'm saying is
this God needs us to be United in
whatever Mission we decide we're going
to
do the
reason because this Mission requires all
hands on
deck if you're not there tonight I'm
going just going to be frank with you if
you're not there tonight to vote this
mission that I will be sharing tonight
then the mission is not going to be
done like seriously like the plan that I
present tonight if we don't vote it or
if we vote against it then it is not
going to be done why because it has to
be yours you have to own it if it's not
yours if it's the pastor's plan then the
plan will
fail it can't be a oh that's the pastor
he's the Evangelist no no no no no
that's not how evangelism is going to
work here
it takes the entire body
am that's why I need you there tonight
beloved
7:30 please be
there God sends us into this land he has
called us here to spy out the land and
yes there are challenges yes this area
is one 7th Day Adventist to a thousand
of the general population that is a
daunting task we have the worst
Adventist to non-adventist ratio in this
city in all of
America it is worse
here and beloved I don't believe that
God has you he think about
that God could have you anywhere else on
this
planet but he says you the ones I've
brought here for this Mission
field how does that make you feel
God has a purpose for every one of us
and beloved we can move with confidence
you want to know why because we know
that God is with
us he told
us he said go into all the world go
teach All Nations baptizing them in the
name of the father Son and the Holy
Ghost teaching them to observe all the
things that I that I command you and
lo I am with you
always so we can advance going forward
knowing that God is what everyone with
us but Satan wants to divide because he
knows if he divides he
conquers listen how do we know God is
with us Matthew 1:23 listen carefully
guys Matthew 123 behold the Virgin shall
be with child and shall bring bring
forth a son and they shall call his name
Emmanuel which being interpreted is
what belov if Jesus is on your side if
Jesus is on our side then God is what
that's his very name in his very name is
the
promise that's the promise
Jesus came to this earth to spy it
out he came understanding the dangers of
the
Kingdom he saw the territories of men's
hearts that there were walls exceeding
high and but Jesus came and said yes I
can I'm going to take these cities I'm
going to take these hearts and you know
what check this out when Jesus came to
fulfill his mission he called 12 men he
chose 12 men and you know what happened
to those 12 men they all were like no we
can't they all forsook
him so you know what Jesus
did
alone he went up
Jesus went
up
alone by
himself and him going up alone by
himself conquered human hearts Broke
Down the
Walls destroyed our
Giants he not only stopped he didn't
just go up on a cross and I if I be
lifted up will draw all men unto me he
went further he went unto
heaven and as a man he went up to heaven
to spy Out Heaven for us y not feel me
heaven is the Heavenly
Canaan so what does he do he goes up to
heaven and he sends us some fruit
yeah he sent down the Holy Spirit saying
hey guys listen I want to show you the
fruit of this land and I just want to
let you know that you are able to come
up and possess this land
see when he poured out the Holy Spirit
upon his church upon his early church it
was an outpouring of the first
fruits the time of the first
fruits and the spirit that he poured
into his people was this Spirit
attack it was a fighting
Spirit
attack because the Bible says listen
carefully beloved you saying why would
the Holy Spirit pour out a fighting
spirit in his people why because we have
to fight the good
fight of church
politics oh no no no no no no sorry
sorry wrong wrong text we have to fight
the good fight of
Faith that's the
fight not the fight of division not the
fight of me against you the fight of
faith the Bible actually says that the
Kingdom of Heaven is taken by Violence
by the violent you know what that text
is saying have you ever read that text
what is this text talking about listen
what it's saying is that if you want the
Kingdom of Heaven you have to fight for
it so God pours out within his Spirit
the his people this fighting Spirit come
come with me Joshua chapter 14 you need
to see this Joshua I'm sorry not Joshua
uh we're going back to numbers chapter
14 Numbers Chapter 14 by the way do you
know all those things that they were
afraid of the the an the the the the
Giants the walls the Canaanites the
amorites do you realize that when the
children of Israel crossed the Jordan
that the Bible says when the Canaanites
heard that God had dried up uh the
Jordan their hearts melted with fear the
obstacle that they had foreseen w we
can't because this God took care of it
when they advanced in
faith the walls remember that the walls
oh they're great walls the walls fell
when they advanced in faith every
obstacle that they had presented this is
why we can't when God when they walked
in God God removed those obstacles for
them numbers 14 verse 5 notice with me
numbers 14 verse5 we're getting there
guys we're we're coming around the bed
numbers 14:5 the Bible says this then
Moses fell on his face before all the
Assembly of the congregation of the
children of Israel and Joshua the son of
nun and Caleb the son of Jeff which were
of them that searched the land rent
their clothes and they spake unto all
the company of the children of Israel
saying the land which we pass through to
search it is an exceeding good land if
the Lord Delight in us then he will
bring us into this land and give it to
us a land which flows with milk and
honey only Rebel not against the Lord
neither fear ye the people of the land
for they are bread for us for their
defense is departed from them and the
Lord is what everyone with us fear them
not but all the congregation bade Stone
them with stone we don't want to hear
what you have to say
anymore we can do what go up Stone
them destroy
them no we're not listening to this
and the Lord said unto Moses verse 11
how long will this people provoke me how
long will it be e they believe me for
all the signs which I have showed among
them I will Smite them with pestilence
and in the rest of the story the Bible
says the Bible says that the children of
Israel are that that Moses interceded
for them and God heard Moses
intercession but check this out guys
because this was
crazy jump jump down with me to verse
25 verse 20 verse 22 verse
22 the Bible says here uh
um verse 22 it says because all those
men which have seen my glory and my
Miracles which I did in Egypt in the
wilderness have tempted me now these 10
times and have not hearkened to my voice
surely they shall not see the land which
I swear to their
fathers neither shall any of them that
provoked me see it but my servant Caleb
because he had another Spirit within him
what is the other Spirit Caleb had
within him what does his name mean
attack what kind of spirit did he
have he had a fighting
Spirit God is with us we are able to go
up and take that
possession we need a fighting Spirit
church for this area we need a fighting
Spirit but but watch
this verse 24
verse 24 the Bible says here uh uh in
fact let me read down a little bit past
verse 24 jump down with me to verse
verse 25 the Bible says now the the
amalekites and the Canaanites dwelt in
the Valley tomorrow turn you and get you
into the Wilderness by the way the red
see what is God saying here go
back check that out guys what does God
say turn go back now let me ask you a
question why is God saying this
say
again okay they asked to die in the
wilderness wait a minute Caleb is
there Joshua's there they're saying
let's do
what no no no no no Joshua and Caleb
what are they
saying they let they're saying they're
saying let's go forward what are the
other 10
saying let's go back so what does God
say he says go back
go
back you guys just take a moment and
don't say anything and just think and
I'm just going to be silent just for a
few seconds for
effect what did God want his people to
do go forward but what happened in the
camp what was there there was what there
was
Division and because there was division
God says no you are not
ready to take the
land you're not
ready you're not
ready because in order to go
forward you have to be on the same
page and beloved this is scary stuff
please nobody take this wrong this is
scary stuff God said we're going to wait
till we are
united we're going to
wait till we have a generation that's
all on the same
page and when the generation's all on
the same page when the church is all on
the same page then we'll go forward but
no no no no no no you're not going
forward like this
nope because the devil knows that if he
can bring division
then we can go forward all we want in
fact come we're we're almost at our
closing text look at this verse
36 verse 39 verse 39 and Moses told
these things unto all the CH all the
children of Israel and the people mourn
greatly and they rose up in the morning
and got them up into the top of the
mountain saying Lo we be here we will go
up onto the place which the Lord has
promised for we have
sinned and Moses said wherefore do you
now transgress the Commandment of the
Lord it shall not Prosper go not up for
the Lord is not among
you and you know what the children of
Israel
did they said we're going up
anyway so now they go forward and guess
what happens when they go
forward they get
beaten the Bible says Moses didn't even
go with them he just stayed in the camp
like y going forward
okay go ahead go right ahead me and the
Ark are staying right
here you see beloved it's not just about
going
forward you know we can say we can say
tonight you know what you know we're
going for we you know that can happen in
churches oh we got these people here and
we're going to do this
and but guess
what that's failure
cuz how are we going to tell the world
to be one when we can't be
one how are we going to do how are we
going to go for forward with a message
that this is what the gospel does when
it doesn't even work in the
church how are we going to do
that
listen Jesus invites us into the
Heavenly
Canan and ultimately what he's saying is
is you can go up you can go
up those who have the fighting Spirit
when Jesus comes again they will go up
and they will get the city because Jesus
went there ahead of them to say Hey
listen I'm there I've been there I've
seen it as a as a man and I want to let
you know you are able to come up and
possess
it but there's another group of people
who get that Spirit too
late and at the end of the Millennium
guess what they try to go up and take
the city but it's the wrong
spirit it's the wrong fighting Spirit
beloved listen to me Satan wants to put
a fighting Spirit within within us that
leads us to fight with one another when
God is trying to put a fighting Spirit
within us to make us all on the same
page fighting for hearts in this
community so I want to make an appeal
right now I'm asking Mark to come
forward because Mark is going to lead us
in prayer
who here is willing to be the first to
say let us go
up we can possess the
land who's going to be the first person
to stand that
says pastor we can do
this God is about to do something here
in this city God is about to use our
church yet all the churches in this area
and and I for one am
saying let's move
unitedly we can do this we can go up and
possess the
land beloved do you believe
it do you believe
it do you want to stand today to say
pastor we need to go
out whatever Satan tries to
do whatever Satan tries to attempt to
get us to take our eyes off of the
prize we're here today to say Satan is
not going to
work we are going to stand by the grace
of God
United because Satan's job is to try to
weaken the
flock and he does it best by dividing
and
conquering by the grace of God let us
pray that not one soul will sat and be
able to take
away let us pray that we will not have a
10 but we will have United a United
people of God
whatever that battle is that you're
facing whatever that on a personal level
say today in your mind God is with me
and I'm going to go up and take what
he's given me